(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-21T06:05:39.432642",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
I'm frog!
みなさん 調子どうですか？
How are you doing, everyone?
How are you?
It's time!
It's time, it's time, it's time, it's time, it's time!
Everybody!
Hello. I'm Mori Calliope from Hololive English Myth,
and welcome to the underworld!
Welcome, welcome, welcome. I have many things to show you.
Check it out. Check out my stage.
Check it out, look at the skulls with the wings in the background!
And oh man, this... this is the best venue in the underworld.
You know it. You know that this is the place to be.
Look at all the deadbeats in the crowd, swinging the lights!
And it's on fire!
すげえな
That's amazing.
Check out the big speakers too.
Yo, that's actually dope.
Thanks, glad you think so. That's me? Correct, that is you.
And you, and you, and you, and you, and you, and you, and you, and you, and you, and you, and you.
That's kind of hot, not gonna lie. Correct?
Correct, it's a little hot in here, but we're about to make it hotter.
Because, guess what you guys, this, this before your eyes is not just a regular place to chill. No, no, no, no, no!
We have performances! Performances, action, romance—maybe not romance, but lots of—lots of performances! So get ready, and thank you for the many congratulations, you guys!
All right. Now, now, for the first performance I want to do, I have something special to show you. Check it out. Oh, it's over here.
All right. Now, for the first performance I want to do, I have something special to show you. Check it out. Oh, it's over here.
I got to go grab—I got to go grab it really quick. Hold on, I'm getting it. It's now in my hand. Okay.
Just so you know, it's—it's in my hands now. Staff-san! Staff-san, it's here! The first song that we're singing today is Wanted, Wasted. Let's go!
Woah, woah
Guess I took a leap, no turning back point to go
Looking deep inside for the cheat to exploit, you know
あいつも こいつも そいつも どいつも
This guy, that guy, everyone, all of them
Driving me crazy, yeah
Wanted, Wasted
Sorry lookin' faced kid, can't stop falling down
Sorry-looking-faced kid, can't stop falling down
Tell me how I'm worthless, show ya where the dirt is
One man's trash is another man's purpose
Day one, flying high
Come tomorrow, let me die
Talk trash, choke and whine
Nothing I own is truly mine
ごっくん
Gokkun
愛されたいのに 出会えない夢を見ているのはなんで？ woah
Even though I want to be loved, why am I dreaming of a dream I can't meet? woah
変えたい現実 胸糞悪くて Highになる
The reality I want to change is sickening and makes me high
やっちゃって やっちゃって
Do it, do it, do it
やっちゃって そのまま傷つけちゃって
Just hurt people like that
期待 裏切る bad ending
A bad ending that betrays expectations
円から抜け出せない エンドロール
Can't escape from the circle, end roll
演奏者は揃いも揃って クズに仕立ててちょうだい
Performers all gathered together, finish me off as scum
整合性 正当性 正義の名の下に
Consistency, legitimacy, in the name of justice
下してやるわ Game maker, undertaker
I'll hand it down, game maker, undertaker
脳天直下 くらえっ
Direct hit right on the crown, take that!
アンアン アンアン 響いけ mayday, mayday
An-an, an-an, resonate, mayday, mayday
タンタン タンタン 鳴らす
Tan-tan, tan-tan, ring it out
聞こえないふりして 逃げられると思ってんの？ w
Playing dumb like you can't hear, do you think you can get away? lol
愛されたいのに 出会えない夢を見ているのはなんで？ woah
Even though I want to be loved, why am I dreaming of a dream I can't meet? woah
変えたい現実 胸糞悪くて Highになる
The reality I want to change is sickening and makes me high
不揃いな声で 喘ぐ声は 天国に近そうな気がしてた
With an insolent voice, the panting voice felt like it was close to heaven
Alright, all night, anger
狂おしく 舞い上がっちまえ
Madly, soar up high
お前が お前が
You, you
Oh my god, oh my god
お前が
You
Oh my god, oh my god
お前が お前が
You, you
Oh my god, oh my god
傷つけちゃって
Hurt me
足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough
足りない 足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough, not enough
Woah
あーもう うぜったい
Ah, so annoying
どうにかしてくんないかし
Do something about it, please
愛されたいのに 出会えない夢を見ているのはなんで？ woah
Even though I want to be loved, why am I dreaming of a dream I can't meet? woah
変えたい現実 胸糞悪くて Highになる
The reality I want to change is sickening and makes me high
不揃いな声で 喘ぐ声は 天国に近そうな気がしてた
With an insolent voice, the panting voice felt like it was close to heaven
Alright, all night, anger
狂おしく 舞い上がっちまえ
Madly, soar up high
足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough
足りない 足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough, not enough
足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough
足りない 足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough, not enough
足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough
足りない 足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough, not enough
足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough
足りない 足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough, not enough
Woah
足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough
足りない 足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough, not enough
Woah
足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough
足りない 足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough, not enough
Woah
足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough
足りない 足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough, not enough
Woah
足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough
足りない 足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough, not enough
Woah
足りない 足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough, not enough
Thank you. Thank you so much, everyone.
Woo, look at him go! But it's not over yet. Because now, I've got another song to sing.
This one's called Nezumi Scheme.
今日 また “ rat race , cat chase ” sing dumb and fall
Today again "rat race, cat chase" sing dumb and fall
but the kingdom of swingdom is open to all
enter the game , it 's a place to make a profit
Enter the game, it's a place to make a profit
rap and swing is a thing now , more for you to scoff at
Rap and swing is a thing now, more for you to scoff at
poisons and haters,
born to hate her,
Shout out to any crazy peeps still in the impact,
Just wanna set fire, I'm wishing I went higher!
veiled 透ける と
Veiled, translucent...
save and reload,
聞き耳なんてないやつから奪う
snatching from those who won't listen.
似て非なる自信と hubris
Similar but not the same, confidence and hubris,
神隠しへと 恐れおののき
swept away, trembling in fear,
黄金でできたハンドルこぎ
rowing with handlebars made of gold,
庇いぶって反りぼって吐け
pretending to protect, arching back and spitting out.
諤々たれ諤々たれ
Speak up, speak up!
シャドウもげんな
Don't snap your shadow either!
チョロざいのそのね ぼらまけしてぬりくがって
Such amateurish tricks, smear them all over.
綺麗なネズミ
A pretty rat!
どんなに振り払っても消えない死なその悪臭は
No amount of perfume can kill the stench of your cheese,
you skeptic, those opinions, kind of septic,
You're my minions, no wait, my biggest fans, internet business women drawing up plans,
why you tryna pin me for a pyramid scheme? I refuse to be a part of any derelict dreams,
swipe over and hear at the screens and they say us
Face silly got to get to saying those prayers,
悪いにびきが もっじゃわせっちゃい ないめくろせのそ
bad vibes all around, nothing going for you!
似て非なる自信と hubris
Similar but not the same, confidence and hubris,
神隠しへと 恐れおののき
swept away, trembling in fear,
黄金でできたハンドルこぎ
rowing with handlebars made of gold,
庇いぶって反りぼって吐け
pretending to protect, arching back and spitting out.
勘違いしてる奴ばかりうんざり
Sick of all these delusional folks,
消したあんたの方には傾かない秤
scales won't tip toward the ones you erased.
あんたのシトスはまだまだくさい
Your secrets still stink so much,
刈り取るまでもねえ 抜群な足は boom! お山の大
no need to reap 'em, legs out of this world, boom! On top of the mountain,
天狗を並べた話せわれを
lining up tengu, speak your mind!
虎の怒り爆できるならやってごらん
If you can explode with the tiger's rage, let's see you try.
全然物足りない その掃除虫喰いは呪えない
Still not nearly enough, gnawing bugs can't be cursed,
怒るもの 必死だからさあ
because wrathful things are desperate, so come on!
似て非なる自信と hubris
Similar but not the same, confidence and hubris,
神隠しへと 恐れおののき
swept away, trembling in fear,
黄金でできたハンドルこぎ
rowing with handlebars made of gold,
庇いぶって反りぼって吐け
pretending to protect, arching back and spitting out.
mortal harm (shallow and shameless)
you put prosthetics, shut up your drivel,
You fake making cheddar, you rat!
ボラマケしてぬりくがってクレイジーネズミ
Smear it all over, you crazy rat!
No amount of perfume can kill the stench of your cheese,
Thank you!
Thank you very much everyone!
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
I take a bow.
Thanks so much! Punch punch punch, go Kelly go, thank you very much!
アンこれ アンこれ アンコレ？ アンコレ？
Encore, encore, encore?
アンコレ？
Encore? Encore?
No, no encore right now. I have something important to introduce to you.
My deadbeat backup dancer's Gaikotsu chan!
My deadbeat backup dancer's Gaikotsu-chan!
Hey, hey!
Gaikotsu chan, mecha kawaii! Gaikotsu-chan, so cute! Hey, hey!
Gaikotsu-chan, mecha kawaii! Gaikotsu-chan, so cute! Hey, hey!
Let's go, let's go, dancer-san, cho kawaii, cho kawaii!
めちゃめちゃいい感じ！
Mecha mecha ii kanji.
Look at Mr. and Mrs. Bones.
Wow, thank you so much for coming. See you later!
Bye-bye!
Man, I'm already worn out from that, but it was so cool
to dance together with my skeletons.
Y'all look cute.
Thank you very much.
They did a great job. I'm glad that I'm glad that you agree.
I'm glad that you're vibing.
No, Mr. Bones, oh it's okay, Mr. and Mrs. Bones.
They may come back, I don't know.
But for now, I do know that I need to I need to chill for a second.
You know, there's one thing that I always really kind of wanted to do, and that was
drink a nice glass of wine during my 3D.
I don't really drink wine very much anymore, but...
I told myself that I would
for this special moment...
is occasion, right?
as occasion, right?
So, that's what I'm going to do.
And the team here at the great Gigole Theater decided to set up something special for me, my own little wine tasting corner.
Rise!
Very nice.
There it is, ladies and gentlemen, check it out, my own little special corner for the tasting of the wine.
It's got a bunch of different types of wine, but I chose the most I found the cheapest one at the convenience store to try for today. So,
this is where we're going to be enjoying some time together.
Are you guys ready?
Swank, very fancy.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Well, I guess it's time Oh, stop some put some water I mean got the wine bottle ready for me.
All right, well,
let me go ahead and grab this and okay.
Well, everybody, should be have a cheers. Box wine? No, no, no, not box wine, not quite.
Convenience store wine?
I asked staff-san to get me the cheapest one.
Um, to hydrate up. Thanks, Watson.
This'll definitely keep me hydrated.
Um, not like I just had a ton of coffee before this or anything, but here we go.
乾杯しましょう！
Let's toast!
Are you guys ready?
You ready for a cheers, everyone? Everyone at home, Calli, your fancy pants Mori.
What can I say? Oh, iine!
What can I say? Oh, nice!
いいね、ガイコツちゃんも乾杯したいね、いいね！
Nice, skellies want to toast too, nice!
All right, well let's cheers! 乾杯！ To 3D, from myth!
All right, well let's cheers! Kampai! To 3D, from myth!
Here we go.
Oh man.
That does taste like convenience store wine.
コンビニワイン、んー、間違いないね！間違いない。
Convenience store wine, mm, no mistake about it! No mistake.
Ah, sometimes you just gotta loosen up, deadbeats. Sometimes you just gotta loosen up.
You don't hear? I wonder, while I'm here drinking this wine maybe you can take a couple screenshots of my face.
Screenshot the shit and use the hashtag "Check out my face".
そして他の表情もありますね、いろんな表情。ちょっと見せて、見せてみよう。Check it out.
And I have other expressions too, all kinds of expressions. Let's show you, let's take a look. Check it out.
My expression do ya ka- "Kawaii! Kawaii!" Hello.
My expression do ya ka- "So cute! So cute!" Hello.
Yo yo yo, cute cute. いろいろありますね。
Yo yo yo, cute cute. There are all sorts.
ツンデレぱ- ツンデレぱ- ちょっと怒ってる。
Tsundere-pa- tsundere-pa- a bit mad.
Oi, oi oi oi!
そして、悲しい、悲しい顔もありますね。悲しい。
And then, sad, there are sad faces too. Sad.
このワインね、もっと安いやつ飲んでみたい！ I would like to try drinking an even cheaper wine, but oh well, this is all we have.
This wine, I'd like to try drinking an even cheaper one! I would like to try drinking an even cheaper wine, but oh well, this is all we have.
そして、びっくり顔。びっくり。
And then, surprised face. Surprised.
うわ！ほんと？ ふざけんな！勘弁して！
Whoa! Really? Are you kidding me? Give me a break!
Give me a break!
うまい。うまいよ。
Delicious. It's good.
But I have to finish this glass. I have to. I promised myself that I would.
I was inspired by, by Lamy-senpai. Lamy-senpai got to drink sake, 日本酒, I think, 日本酒 it was, on stream for her 3D debut, so I figured I'm going to do the same.
I was inspired by, by Lamy-senpai. Lamy-senpai got to drink sake, Nihonshu, I think, Nihonshu it was, on stream for her 3D debut, so I figured I'm going to do the same.
As one of the only alcohol- okay members of EN.
As one of the only alcohol-okay members of EN.
Let's see what chat has to say. Kawaii? Oh, wamy! Wamy, wamy, wamy!
Based. Lamy's great.
Where's the gaa?
Chat, you're right. Hold on, hold on, I got you, I got you. All right, listen. Listen, よく聞いて。
Chat, you're right. Hold on, hold on, I got you, I got you. All right, listen. Listen, hear me out.
Gaa!
If you missed it, I'll do it one more time. Hold on. We're almost done.
All right, done with the wine. ワイン終わりです。
All right, done with the wine. Wine time is over.
I can't- I can't do too much because, you know, we have stuff to do.
Oh! Hey!
What's going on here?
Little skurling tons?
Hey, buddies!
Thank you for all the super chats, everyone!
These are- this is my garden of super chats.
All my deadbeats send in superas, they're coming in with roses, coming in hot. Look at 'em gather.
Aw. Hey, buddies! My superas.
Aw, so cute!
Hold on.
Oh, you're a good deadbeat.
You're a good deadbeat.
Who's been a good- Hey, it's me! It's you!
可愛いね！
So cute!
What? What's that?
What's that, deadbeat? You want me to step on you?
Oh gosh. Okay, hold on. Hold on. Deadbeat, you've been bad.
悪いこ？悪いこ？ Bad deadbeat, bad.
Bad kid? Bad kid? Bad deadbeat, bad.
You've been bad. Uh uh. Bonk, bonk, bonk, bonk, bonk!
You've been bad. Uh-uh. Bonk, bonk, bonk, bonk, bonk!
Yes, tasukaru! Tasukaru!
Yes, that helps! That helps!
Oh, you know what?
You know what I also have?
I have my scythe.
My scythe, my- what is it?
Well, I have- I have my big- my big scythe, you know, Ricky, right?
But I have something else I want to show you, yeah?
おかに何かありますよ、特別なやつ。
There's something else, a special one.
An instrument, you saw it before.
Hold on, I'm going to go grab it again, okay?
Just stay right there. Stay right there, I'm going to get the scythe.
Ah, I got it!
I got it, I got it. Everyone, look!
It's the Rocky Bass!
Pretty cool, right? Horamite, めっちゃ素敵ですねー！
Pretty cool, right? Look at this, it's super nice!
You can play it, of course. I'm- I'm messing around.
But, but, you only... you don't only have to play it.
But, you don't only have to play it.
No, no, no.
You can use it as a weapon if you want.
What I mean?
What do I mean?
I'll show you, I'll show you, okay?
I'll show you, okay?
I've been training a lot, so.
Okay, get the stance perfect, and then...
Thrust stroke,
uppercut,
and mawaru...
and peck around! Hah!
Ee kanji desu ne.
Isn't it cool?
Look at it.
It has multiple purposes.
Did you know, back in the day,
farmers used to use the scythe to harvest the crops and the grass, cut the grass like this?
farmers used the scythe to harvest crops?
Yeah?
That was the original use of the scythe.
And then us reapers decided that it was such a waste of a great tool... to not use them to take people's lives, as, you know, murder weapon.
And reapers use them as murder weapons.
Aw, look at the little dead beat playing!
He's having so much fun! Aw, look at how cute!
He's having so much fun! Aw, how cute!
All right, so as I was saying, this is usually how, you know, we reap the super chats and the souls and stuff like that.
This is how we reap super chats and souls.
Down in the fields, we kind of do a similar thing to what the farmers used to do back in the day,
Down in the fields, we do a similar thing
what? En-nichi shiteru?
to what farmers did back then. En-nichi?
Teddy, what are you doing?
Hayashii? What's this?
Are you stealing the super chats?
Hey! Oi oi oi, dead beat, stop! Super chats on the shindelu?
Hey! Stop! Super chats on the shinderu?
Majika?
Hey, wait! No, no, no, not that!
Hey, wait! No, not that!
Wait, that's my scythe!
Come, bench stair!
Wait a minute, I can fight back!
You want to fight me dead beat?
That's fine, you do know who you're dealing with right, though.
All right, you know who you're dealing with.
I am the Grim Reaper's first apprentice.
Okay then, if it's a fight you want, it's a fight you'll get.
If it's a fight you want, it's a fight you'll get.
Fuzaken na!
Mada ikiteru? Hisshou live?
Oi oi oi, that's not funny dead beat, stop laughing at me!
Stop laughing at me, dead beat!
We're going to have to use more than just weaponry to get back at this dead beat.
We need more than weapons to get back at you.
We'll figure something else out.
Come at me!
Let's finish this.
Get Mori-dated! Woo!
Yeah, baby! Burn, baby, burn!
Burn so many evil skeletons!
But who's going to help me enjoy my 3D now?
But who's going to help me enjoy my 3D?
Those guys were my backup dancers, camera crew...
Those guys were my backup dancers, crew...
I didn't think they'd get so money-hungry and rowdy!
I didn't think they'd get so rowdy!
Oh, will you guys hang out with me?
My friends are here! My friends came to party, everyone!
My friends are here to party, everyone!
As you expected, I've got my buddies here, my myth friends. They came to hang out with me.
I've got my myth friends here with me.
So, I guess it's time to... to do myth-related things.
So, I guess it's time for myth things.
Come on! Come on! Come on out, friends!
Come on out, friends!
But here's the catch: you can't see them. They're invisible. They're invisible, I think.
But here's the catch: they're invisible.
They're going to be my camera people.
Well, I have... I have two camera guests today.
I have two camera guests today.
Come on over! We've got... Nino-mae Inanis is here.
Come on over! Ninomae Ina'nis is here.
I can't believe I died!
Ouchan, help me!
Ina-chan, help me!
And Ame! Ame's here too! You can't see them, though.
And Ame's here too! You can't see them.
They're mysterious spirits... drifting in the wilderness of the underworld. Hi!
Mysterious spirits in the underworld. Hi!
And you've got the camera now, you've got all the power. So they're going to help me get the best angles!
They're going to help me get the best angles!
And then I think we have Kiwawa and Gu-a in here, yeah?
And we have Kiwawa and Gura in here, yeah?
Yay!
Hello! Hello everybody!
You look so live, have to stare...
You guys look so live! Have to stare!
Look at this crowd! This is cool.
We get to go home after this right, Kiara? Well, we'll talk about that a little bit later.
We get to go home after this, right, Kiara?
Well, we'll talk about that a little bit later.
So... So, I got to... I got to say, um, I'm worried about Gawr Gura.
So... I got to say, um,
I'm worried about Gawr Gura.
Your voice sounds like it's dying.performance.
Your voice sounds like it's dying.
Performance!
Oh, yeah! You reaped my voice! Can you stop reaping my voice, please?
Oh, yeah! You reaped my voice!
Can you stop reaping my voice, please?
No!
Won't do that.
What do you guys think of this? This crazy stage?
What do you guys think of this?
This crazy stage?
It's on fire!
It is on fire!
Bring down the house.
Is Ina on me?
It's working!
Ina is on the camera!
Ina's on the camera!
Yeah, Ina's on the camera now. Ina's in control.
Yeah, Ina's on the camera now.
Ina's in control.
Ina's in control. All right.
Well, we're going to hold that thought and, Ame, what do you want me to do? Give me something to do.
Well, we're going to hold that thought, and Ame,
what do you want me to do? Give me something to do.
You first.
You know what I'm going to ask.
Oh, I do?
Are you going to ask me to do the worm?
Do the worm!
Do it! Do the worm! Do the worm!
You know what? All right, here's the thing.
I'm going to do it to prove it can be done, okay? Ina? Ina?
I'm going to do it to prove it can be done,
okay? Ina? Ina?
No, it's Ina.
No, you put that camera...
I have one advice, Calli. How about, you know, if it's difficult for you, you know, the worm, how you normally push yourself up with the arms...
I have one advice, Calli. How about, if it's
difficult for you, the worm, how you normally...
You can... you can bounce yourself off of your boobies.
You can... you can bounce
yourself off of your boobies.
What the... Really? You want to have... You want to fucking...
What the... Really? You want to have...
You want to fucking...
You want to fucking com... bench that? Okay. All right, all other girls.
You want to fucking com... bench that?
Okay. All right, all other girls.
Yeah, work it.
Hey! You saw me lift up to... All right, hold on. No, it's okay.
Hey! You saw me lift up to...
All right, hold on. No, it's okay.
No, it's a good worm. Good worm! One more worm!
No, it's a good worm.
Good worm! One more worm!
Do it! Do it! Do it! Do it!
Nice, nice! She's worming! The song's end and she's worming!
Nice, nice! She's worming!
The song's ended and she's worming!
Okay, okay. You can get up! You can get up! You can get up!
Okay, okay. You can get up!
You can get up! You can get up!
Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy.
I'm going to get you for this. Our payback.
Wait, fuck, you know.
This is only the beginning here, you see.
Okay, Kiara, do you have anything... Excuse me, ma'am!
Okay, Kiara, do you have anything...
Excuse me, ma'am!
No, not you. You're the camera person. Okay, okay, fine. Watson is in control. What is your request, Kiara?
No, not you. You're the camera person.
Okay, Watson is in control. What is your request, Kiara?
And... so, I want something cute, and that will be without music, but can you please do the caramel dansen dance with your hands on your... on your... Do you know it?
And... so, I want something cute, and that will be
without music, but can you please do the caramel dansen...
I do. You're taking me way back.
All right, here we go.
And then, full body and also close-up, please, camera, both.
And then, full body and also close-up,
please, camera, both.
You have a... That's an impossible request, client.
That is a tall order. I guess a zoom in. Okay, I'll zoom in. Yeah, However you see fit to do it, Watson.
That is a tall order. I guess a zoom in. Okay, I'll zoom in.
However you see fit to do it, Watson.
Okay.
This is the boom-boom. I'll just say, yeah, yeah.
Yeah!
It's the caramel dansen! It's okay, we'll just... we'll fix it. Let me do it more tense. It's like this!
It's the caramel dansen! It's okay, we'll just...
we'll fix it. Let me do it more tense. It's like this!
Okay! Okay! Okay! Okay!
You guys are going to tire me up before the end of all of this.
You guys are going to tire me up
before the end of all of this.
Isn't it my turn?
No, okay, girl.
What's your request?
A cartwheel. What was that? Cartwheel?
Cartwheel. Are you kidding me?
No.
Girl, when she do it, it's so dangerous. All right, I'm trying to get you in. Let's go.
Girl, when she do it, it's so dangerous.
All right, I'm trying to get you in. Let's go.
Cartwheel! Let's go! Cartwheel! All right, here we go.
You said difficult!
Come on, man. Okay.
That was an action roll. Action roll?
Yeah.
Oh, okay. All right.
I thought you wanted another one.
No, no, no, no, die! I thought you wanted another one.
No, no, no, no. I thought you wanted another one.
All right. All right, well, I guess that's it for all the...
All right. All right, well,
I guess that's it for all the...
No! No! All right, all right.
What do you want me to do, Ina? Well, is my turn on the camera.
What do you want me to do, Ina?
Well, it's my turn on the camera.
All right.
I want you to give us... Wait, what? Turn around because I'm scared. I'm scared!
I want you to give us... Wait, what?
Turn around because I'm scared. I'm scared!
Why are you running? Why are you running? Leave me be!
Why are you running? Why are you running?
Leave me be!
Why are you running?
No, no, no. Yada.
No, no, no. No way.
Okay, okay, okay. I want you to give us the most cutest...
Okay, okay, okay.
I want you to give us the cutest...
Moe, moe, kyun!
Thank you for coming to Calliope Mori's 3D!
Aye, aye!
You can't run away! You can't run away! You can't run away!
Moe, moe, kyun!
Yeah.
Put body and put your heart into it.
Come on.
Come on, you can do it.
I've been waiting for years.
Do you want to cause the entirety of these skeletons to cringe so hard they die a second time?
Well, it's some fire.
Might as well put out the fire with some, you know, embarrassment, second-hand embarrassment.
With tears of joy from dead beats.
Is this really what you want, Deadbeats?
Well, let's look at chat.
Chat, is this really what you want? They're saying yes! They're saying yes!
Don't hesitate. Just do it! Just do it!
Just do it!
All right, fine.
All right, Calliope,
let me think about the choreography.
Okay, she's thinking.
Ooh, cute.
Spin! Yeah!
Okay, okay.
What's the best camera angle?
Oh, for real.
All right, start from here.
Oh, cute!
All right, we can do a little, yeah. Oh, kawaii!
Okay.
All right, here I go. Here I go.
Moe, moe, kyun!
You son of a-
It's all your fault!
This is the day that I die.
It was good! It was good!
It was good! It was good! Cute!
Oh, look at that panty- Oh, this one!
Oh, cute! Oh, cute! Kyun!
Kyun! No problem!
Kyun!
Oh, I missed it.
Wait, what?
Am I going to get banned? What?
No, no, no. Look at the nice shoes.
Ooh, shoes! Pretty nice, right?
You want to give everybody a full-body look?
Yes! Full-body scan!
What else am I saying? What else did I say in rehearsal?
You got to what? Show the what?
Show the what? What'd you say?
Get in the slit!
Oh, get in the slit!
Get in the slit is the command!
I did not!
Yeah, you did!
Hey, we're exposing you now, okay?
I did not. Oh, hi, keep it-
Deadbeats. I love the beat.
You know what you're doing.
Oh, I did not.
You have any up-close things you guys want to see?
Ooh, your eyeballs.
I mean, let people see your eyeballs.
How close can we get? Your eyes are fascinating.
Oh, glowing.
Ooh.
Glowing! So scary!
I think we saw your brain.
Oh, really?
It wasn't very big, was it?
I don't know. What kind of hot take is that?
Check the video.
Enna, why are you doing that with the camera?
What? What's that?
We got you all on video.
Oh, yeah, Enna, why are you getting so weird with the camera right now?
It's not me!
Oh. You know what?
This is for Watame Senpai.
Oh, Watame senpai!
Watame senpai!
Let me let me check- Let me kind of
pretend to be walking like- What was the-
Watame senpai! Watame senpai! Impression!
Good walking!
Watame what? Watame what?
Enna!
What's this for you?
Senpai dasi!
You good, Enna?
You good, bro?
Here's the other one.
This is Watame senpai's property.
Left side, right side.
Watame senpai doesn't-
I wonder.
Hold on.
I'm sorry.
Oh, shit! They emptied out!
Oh!
Here we go! Here we go!
I have no words! I've seen this before somewhere!
The fire's going to hold me there!
Senchou, look at me!
I have- I have no words! I'm Senchou! Look at me all my responsibility!
Ahoy!
Ahoy! What's up? You're on a trampoline!
See, now I'm having fun, now that now that you guys aren't
puppeteering me like evil geniuses.
I-
I just realized.
I have- I have some power here.
Power of the ancient ones! What does that mean?
I'll tell you to freeze!
Now.
Oh, now I can-
Enna is moving her arms!
What are you doing?
Enna is posing her-
No, wait!
You're like puppet figures! Why can't I move?
No! Puppet feet!
What's she doing? Puppet!
What is she doing to me?
Feet!
No, no, no, feet!
This is evil!
You're evil, Reina!
Okay, you're back.
Oh, my god.
I don't know if you guys could see that, but there were forces moving me. I think it was
I think it was Enna.
Not that you're dead here, you know, but I still have my power.
Where ghost so yeah, we can move stuff. I guess so.
Tell me I can I can move objects as well. You can.
You can.
You wouldn't go ahead—
Do you have the power to move stuff to a minute?
You want to try?
You try first.
It's your idea.
Okay.
All right.
Well, let me get the scythe. A kama.
uh 普通の鎌
Uh, futsū no kama.
I'm gonna get the regular scythe.
Nice, that's cute.
Here it is.
What do you think? Is it tricky?
It's very key.
It's very kiki.
Fresh, fresh kiki.
Uh, no kiki. Just ricky.
Kiki ricky.
Kiki is the base.
Here, would you like to hold it?
Ina? Ina of the void?
Hey, what did you say? Would you like to hold it?
Then we know she's just holding it.
No, no, no. Holding it with her powers.
Yeah, with her powers.
Kind ghost powers.
That's right.
And sour.
This is my final power.
Science!
The homunculus gear.
Final attack.
So cool.
Zappa!
Kakkoii.
Hey, what are you doing? What are you doing with that scythe? Stop, stop.
She's just—
What are you doing?
I don't know what to do about it.
It's fine.
Look at how well— You can really talk with that scythe, huh?
Yeah.
How do you even do it?
Looking good. Please don't hurt me.
I'll think about it.
Oh god.
I guess, wait, hold on.
Let's see how low I can go.
Oh! Are we doing limbo or—
It is limbo time, lady.
All right, limbo. I have it there.
Oh, fine.
Fine, fine. Over here.
That's a good height.
How low can you go?
How low? Why is the scythe-
No dancing!
I don't have control.
Can you hold it properly?
How low can you go?
How low?
Can you go?
It takes a lot of power. Can you go?
All right, we gotta switch.
She's just dancing too much.
I'm dancing too much.
Ready today!
Okay, okay. We can't see.
Okay.
You know, back on the camera.
All right, I got the camera.
Watson's got the scythe.
Oh god, Watson-
Watson's got the scythe!
Oh no!
Who keep- Who keep vomiting in freight?
All right, the detector.
You said I was- I was moving too much.
That was pretty cool.
All right.
You said I was- I was moving too much.
That was pretty cool.
All right, how low can you go?
Yeah, you go.
How low? Okay, at this-
Oh! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Limbo time!
Yeah! Nice! All right, final level.
How low are you going to make me go? Is this all the way?
So.
How low can you go?
Don't hurt yourself! Can you go?
Oh my goodness! Can you go?
Limbo!
Yeah! Nice!
I went low! I went low!
How come you're more flexible than I am?
Everybody's more flexible.
Look at that!
Oh, the wink!
Kiwawa, you're pretty flexible!
You had all those dance moves!
No, no, no! And you- you did like this.
That bon- bon odori-ish.
I felt something there.
No, you didn't.
Okay, I did not.
Do we have time for one more request?
Yeah, we have time for one more.
Can you give us like- some sick kime-pose and then I want the camera to do like a 360 as if you're like a figurine.
Ooh, that's a good idea!
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay.
Let's see. What is- maybe with the scythe?
Oh, with the scythe?
Cool.
Yeah, okay, okay. Got it. It's gone.
All right.
Oh oh oh.
And now 360, yeah, slowly and smoothly.
Oh yeah, walk slow. I mean, smoothly.
[Laughs]
Ganbare, ganbare!
Ah, it's a figurine on sale right now! Available for pre-order!
You should do the pop-up parade figure, though.
Oh yeah, that doesn't have the scythe, though. It's like a- yeah!
Look at that!
Oh, we got you with the scythe version.
Oh yeah, that looks good with the scythe, too.
Yeah.
Just like my figurine!
Yeah, it's just like my- wait, look at the scythe there! Exactly like my anime figures.
I'm really good at standing still. Check it out!
Nice!
Is that a DIY, Wawa?
Oh, I'm still- I'm still cleaning it!
I'm- I'm eating the camera bit.
There- this is-
This is my camera work. I'm doing that, yeah.
Yeah, that's-
No! That was clean! Don't eat that!
Yeah, that's right. Ame's skills are super good with the camera.
Anyway, this is a cool, for-sure impose. This is the last thing you see before you die.
Oh.
Yeah.
And then can I- can I get the camera once she settled?
Hey, you're- you're getting- you were working on the camera, just-
Okay, okay.
I want to get like- ooh. Okay.
気を付けて
Watch out!
やばい やばい 気を付けて
Yabe, yabe, watch out!
あ、待って、やばい
Ah, wait, yabe—
Damn it!
ね、みんな、ストップ、やめて、ストップ
Hey guys, stop, don't, stop!
あー、もう！
Ah, jeez!
Little deadbeat, you've, you've been bad.
Bad, bad, little deadbeat.
I got to punish you, punishment time.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
あー、もう、踏んじゃう、踏んじゃう、踏んじゃう
Ah, jeez, I'm gonna step on you!
やめて！
Stop it!
あー！
Ah!
I'm banned!
That's it, Watson! That's it, Watson!
Ina, you know, on the camera!
That was not me!
You can't always do that!
Hold on.
I'm banned, it's over!
It's over, woo, let's go, 3D debut and I'm banned from YouTube.
画面に出たお前ら！
Everyone who appeared on screen!
出禁だ、おい！
You're banned, hey!
Thank you ladies for coming to party with me for a little bit.
That was a lot of fun.
I love...
Hey!
Very cute!
Thank you very much Gura and Ina and Watson as well for joining in.
Thank you so much you guys are the best.
I wish I could control the camera, go kill her times.
Yeah, we'll have more chances down the line.
Yeah, definitely.
Thank you Ina, thank you...
On the camera.
You guys are the best.
Thank you Gura, see you later.
I'll see you guys later.
Bye bye! See you later friends!
See you later friends!
There they go.
Off into the distance.
Goodbye friends!
And now we are here with only Mowgli.
If you don't mind, I'm going to get a little, a little drinky.
Where's my drink? Hold on, I have my, my water.
Mazu, I'll drink... Kiara's water bottle... cause she's not here.
She's not here, that's okay.
She's resting. Anyway.
Uh, so I would say I'm all alone now.
Sadness.
But I'm not alone, because I have some friends here with me now.
Uh you guys have seen me do some 3D stuff in the past, right?
Not holo, but like concert and stuff.
And at those times I always asked like my Holo, Holo-sempai to come hang out with me.
But this time, this time, uh I wanted to do something special.
So, um...
Yo? Question mark? Question mark? Friend time, more guests, indeed.
More guests are here. Um...
So, let's see, I see a lot of guests, guests, A-chan, Adam...
There's no Adam! There's no Adam!
Ey yo! Ey yo! Uh...
A lot of people are saying kohai. Not kohai!
In fact, 先輩が来てくれた。
In fact, senpai came to visit.
So, without further ado, ladies and gentlemen, let's do a song.
Here we go.
Oh it’s a fine day to die, ain’t it? Ya deadbeats!
It’s always been “Life vs. Me” since the earth stood still
Cryin’ “Mercy, mercy” as they run for the hills
Gotcha in my sights and that’s all that it takes
Watch ya bend to the scythe but call it nature’s mistake
Fate’s your friend for today, but lock your doors for tonight
Play pretend that you escaped me ’til I jump you like sike
In spite of freaks like you, the mood could use a lift
Was working easily until I felt a graveyard shift
Hello 死神！「生命なんてチリ紙」ってか？
Hello Death! You think "life's just toilet paper"?
Calli is 狩る側なら俺らジェリー
If Calli's the hunter, we're jelly
Even Mr. Saitama never kill us
そのアブラガッシュな鎌でできるかな？
Can you do it with that greasy scythe?
腐ってたって鯛 BOOGEY VOXX freshでtight
Even rotten sea bream, BOOGEY VOXX fresh and tight
Walking deadみたいに詰め寄ってbite
Closing in like the walking dead to bite
テーブルで眠る未払いのbill
The unpaid bill sleeping on the table
利息までたっぷりいただしきにきたってワケさ
We came to collect with plenty of interest
「お迎え」は NO THANK YOU 生き返って Let’s go crazy
"Welcome" is NO THANK YOU, come back to life and let's go crazy
これは WARNING! WARNING! WARNING!
This is WARNING! WARNING! WARNING!
アブナイ んじゃない？
Isn't it dangerous?
生と死を壊すのアタシたち
We are the ones breaking life and death
誰もマネできないコトしちまおう
Let's do something nobody can imitate
Dead line 飛び越えて笑い歌っちゃう
Jump over the deadline, laugh and sing out
Say 屍, zombie, 死神, the party killers have arrived
Say corpse, zombie, death god, the party killers have arrived
Can find us hanging by the mausoleum doors living our best lives
Alright, it’s fine, ’cause all in due time, this scythe’s designed to reach your head
For now, party down like 気軽に行こう ’til I bury you dead
For now, party down like let's take it easy ’til I bury you dead
生まれつきの才能が孤独を生むのはご承知の通りだが
As you know, inborn talent breeds loneliness, but
あまりに強い孤独には引力のようなパワー
Such intense loneliness has a gravitational power
さながらたった２本だけの花束の薔薇
Like a bouquet of just two roses
俺らならラカショーで稼ぐ a million dollar
For us, making a million dollars easily
輪廻すら俺らを中心に据える
Centering even reincarnation around us
だからいつも自由に生きて自由に死ねる
That's why we always live and die freely
四十九日目の judgement
Judgment on the 49th day
鼻に脱脂綿
Cotton in the nose
詰めた undead
Stuffed undead
キミの背中でピース
Peace on your back
Cranking tunes in the night? Giving humans a fright?
Am I losing it? Are un-alivers actually alright?
Wish ya told me earlier, so tell ya what we should do
Death is lonelier than hell, so might as well be a crew
A violent spell to debut, the silent killer plus two
I got a friend in the undead and suddenly it’s all new
No more “bones to pick” or skeletons in the closet
Hunter hanging with the prey, you know she’s finally lost it
Cranking tunes in the night? Giving humans a fright?
Am I losing it? Are un-alivers actually alright?
Wish ya told me earlier, so tell ya what we should do
Death is lonelier than hell, so might as well be a crew
A violent spell to debut, the silent killer plus two
I got a friend in the undead and suddenly it’s all new
Oh it’s a fine day to die, ain’t it? Ya deadbeats!
Oh, it's a fine day to die, ain't it? Ya deadbeats!
We interrupt today’s usual broadcast to deliver an exceptionally dire piece of news...
We interrupt today's usual broadcast to deliver an exceptionally dire piece of news...
that Mori Calliope is on the hunt. Beware!
It’s always been “Life vs. Me” since the earth stood still
It's always been "Life vs. Me" since the earth stood still
Cryin’ “Mercy, mercy” as they run for the hills
Crying "Mercy, mercy" as they run for the hills
Gotcha in my sights and that’s all that it takes
Gotcha in my sights and that's all that it takes
Watch ya bend to the scythe but call it nature’s mistake
Watch ya bend to the scythe but call it nature's mistake
Fate’s your friend for today, but lock your doors for tonight
Fate's your friend for today, but lock your doors for tonight
Play pretend that you escaped me ’till i jump you like sike!
Play pretend that you escaped me 'till I jump you like sike!
In spite of freaks like you, the mood could use a lift
Was working easily until I felt a graveyard shift!
Hello 死神！「生命なんてトイレットペーパー」ってか？
Hello Shinigami! "Life is just toilet paper," or what?
Calli is 狩る側 なら 俺らジェリー
Calli is the hunter, while we're the jelly
Even Mr. Saitama never kill us
そのアブダガッシュな鎌で できるかな？
Can you do that with your abstruse scythe?
腐って たって膿 Boogey Voxx fresh で tight
Rotting yet pusy, Boogey Voxx fresh and tight
Walking dead みたいに 詰め寄っ て bite (wow)
Closing in like the walking dead to bite (wow)
テーブル で 眠る 未払い の bill
The unpaid bill sleeping on the table
利子 まで たっぷり いただき に き た って ワケ さ
Come to collect it all with interest added, see?
「お迎え」は no thank you
A "welcome" is no thank you
生き返って let’s go crazy
Come back to life and let's go crazy
これ は warning! warning! warning!
This is a warning! warning! warning!
アブナイ ん じゃ ない ？
Isn't it dangerous?
生 と 死 を 壊す の アタシ たち
We are the ones breaking life and death
誰も マネ できない コト しま しょ
Let's do something nobody else can copy
dead line 飛び越えて 笑い歌っちゃう！
Jump across the deadline and laugh and sing!
Say 姦屍 , zombie , 死神 , The party killers have arrived
Say ghoul, zombie, grim reaper, the party killers have arrived
Can find us hanging by the mausoleum doors living our best lives
Alright, it’s fine, ’cause all in due time, this scythe’s designed to reach your head
Alright, it's fine, 'cause all in due time, this scythe's designed to reach your head
For now, party down like 気楽 に 行こう ’ til i bury you dead
For now, party down like taking it easy 'til I bury you dead
(What, you got somethin’ to say?)
(What, you got somethin' to say?)
生まれつきの才能が孤独を生むのはご承知の通りだが
As you know, innate talent breeds loneliness,
あまりに強い孤独には引力のようなパワー
But such strong loneliness has a gravitational power
さながらたった２本だけの花束の薔薇
Like a bouquet of just two roses
俺らならラクショーで稼ぐ a million dollar
We'd easily earn a million dollars
輪廻すら俺らを中心に据える
Centering even reincarnation around us
だからいつでも自由に生きて自由に死ねる
So we can always live freely and die freely
四十九日目の judgement
The judgment on the 49th day
鼻に脱脂綿
Cotton in the nose
詰めた undead
Packed undead
キミの背後でピース
Peace behind your back
Cranking tunes in the night? Giving humans a fright?
Am I losing it? Are un-alivers actually alright?
Wish ya told me earlier, so tell ya what we should do
Death is lonelier than hell, so might as well be a crew
A violent spell to debut, the silent killer plus two
I got a friend in the undead and suddenly it’s all new
I got a friend in the undead and suddenly it's all new
No more “bones to pick” or skeletons in the closet
No more "bones to pick" or skeletons in the closet
Hunter hanging with the prey, you know she’s finally lost it
Hunter hanging with the prey, you know she's finally lost it
ひっくり返したら
When you turn it upside down
死神 も undead ! ?
Even the grim reaper is undead!?
これ は warning! warning! warning!
This is a warning! warning! warning!
アブナイ ん じゃ ない ？
Isn't it dangerous?
生 と 死 を 壊す の アタシ たち
We are the ones breaking life and death
誰も マネ できない コト しま しょ
Let's do something nobody else can copy
dead line 飛び越えて 笑い歌っちゃう！
Jump across the deadline and laugh and sing!
Say 姦屍 , zombie , 死神 , The party killers have arrived
Say ghoul, zombie, grim reaper, the party killers have arrived
Can find us hanging by the mausoleum doors living our best lives
Alright, it’s fine, ’cause all in due time, this scythe’s designed to reach your head
Alright, it's fine, 'cause all in due time, this scythe's designed to reach your head
For now, party down like 気楽 に 行こう ’ til i bury you dead
For now, party down like taking it easy 'til I bury you dead
二十一グラム は
21 grams
まだ 消え ちゃう ない
Won't vanish just yet
これ は
This is
やっぱり
After all
これ は warning! warning! warning!
This is a warning! warning! warning!
アブナイ ん じゃ ない ？
Isn't it dangerous?
生 と 死 を 壊す の アタシ たち
We are the ones breaking life and death
誰も マネ できない コト しま しょ
Let's do something nobody else can copy
dead line 飛び越えて 笑い歌っちゃう！
Jump across the deadline and laugh and sing!
Say 姦屍 , zombie , 死神 , The party killers have arrived
Say ghoul, zombie, grim reaper, the party killers have arrived
Can find us hanging by the mausoleum doors living our best lives
Alright, it’s fine, ’cause all in due time, this scythe’s designed to reach your head
Alright, it's fine, 'cause all in due time, this scythe's designed to reach your head
For now, party down like 気楽 に 行こう ’ til i bury you dead
For now, party down like taking it easy 'til I bury you dead
Well, I guess exceptions can be made (Maybe)
Thank you very much everyone!
Thank you!
Thank you! First, we have a show, guys!
やめろって！
Stop it!
本当に！
Seriously!
怖いって！
It's scary!
Well, they said they're very happy to have a chance to perform with me on stage because we always wanted to,
right? We always wanted to perform together on the same stage. So now, before their musical activities together end, we get a chance to do that, and I think that's really amazing.
So we've got another song to do. This will be the last song for today. This song is called Crown. Please enjoy.
声が聞こえたんだ
I heard a voice,
“World is yours.”
"World is yours."
神様は手帳返事が上手
God's responses are too quick,
Geek to da JOBS, NEMO to da JAWS.
でも 俺 の マインド は “触んじゃねえよ, JOCKs”
But my mind is, "Don't touch me, JOCKs"
'cause I’m nerd mother f**ker
'cause I'm a nerd motherf***er,
Rapで現実にするJokes
making jokes reality through rap.
文脈を蹂虆したらもう戻れない
Once you break the context, you can't go back.
だけど この 世界 じゃ 誰も 俺 ら を 殺せない な
But in this world, nobody can kill us.
don’t be afraid my homies エゴサーチの結果くらいじゃプライドは汚せないね baby
Don't be afraid, my homies. An ego search won't taint our pride, baby.
街で見かけたboys & girlsのシャツに俺たちのマーク
The mark of us on the shirts of the boys & girls seen on the street.
好きな時に食うとんかつ お前も立ってりゃいつかそうなる
Eating tonkatsu whenever you like, if you stand too, you'll get there someday.
病む夜 悩む夜 一人で飲むのアルコール 俺のこの声が明日の お前のバックボーン
Sick nights, troubled nights, drinking alcohol alone. My voice will be your backbone tomorrow.
テキーラは1shotじゃつまんねえ いつものclub いつもの席でお前のことを待っている
Tequila isn't fun as just one shot. Waiting for you at the usual club, usual seat.
never imagined my passion would lead to a success story
shout outs to every overworldian who got love for me
wanna share that fabulous glory, one-man's world got nothin' for me
self-serving, walked the road alone, nope, high hopes for the-- stop it, you bore me
remember re-hi days, led into the smoke-filled nights
a pack of big-dreaming strays beneath those tokyo nights
some broken foreign kid exploring bridges between worlds, found a voice amongst the noise, hey listen, I was that girl
looked for the chance in my midst, would not back down or back out, but I was pessimistic, almost missed it, drowning in doubts
will I ever make it big? sure, isn't worth it to try? like could I really see my picture on that billboard sign
am I outta my mind? crashin' back to days I felt spineless, 仲間の優しさで I was saved by that kindness
Am I outta my mind? Crashin' back to days I felt spineless, I was saved by that kindness.
what I find is, like the pages of the story that binds us, we progressed, became our best, each footstep to here defined us
すっ転んでこぼれていった コインと涙の数限りないけど ただ走った先たどり着いた 今叫ぶよ「幸せだ」
Coins and tears spilled over as we tumbled endlessly, but we ran forward and arrived, now shouting "I'm happy!"
yo calli, こんなところまでありがとう ところで俺たちが明日吸う予定のそっちの空気の味はどう？
Yo Calli, thanks for getting this far. By the way, how does the air taste over there where we're supposed to breathe tomorrow?
ほら見て見てsenpai I come a long way!
Look, look senpai, I come a long way!
still making moves from the views we knew from back in the day
俺もそうだ長すぎる1年 お待たせどうもさん
Me too, it's been too long a year, thanks for waiting.
止まりそうな夜は背中を見ていたよ、お嬢さん
On nights when we almost stopped, I was watching your back, young lady.
had my back from the start, so i gotta say “ありがとう” be it this world or the next, bet we'll meet on every road
Had my back from the start, so I gotta say "Arigatou". Be it this world or the next, bet we'll meet on every road.
still lie awake in my bed, above cds I couldn't sell, life what 's you make, so instead, let it be your reason to rebel
Still lie awake in my bed, above CDs I couldn't sell. Life's what you make, so instead, let it be your reason to rebel.
far as this reaper can tell, I was investing in me, penniless, sleeping in hell; that was a test for my being
seeing this dream brought to life right before me, every song that restored me
me early mornings and shores things they all led to your mori
early mornings, unsure things, they all led to your Mori.
always stay roaring into mics and facing all that comes at me, still gonna pour my "life blood" into this, so death can be happy
no map or compass for us, one thing that never did change, we're still the same wild vagabonds from a far-off age
but in the name of refraining from dragging on, think fast! the victory march is on, so i'll tag along this mic-pass!
本当のチャンスは俺たちに踏み絵を強要しない この才能をこのダチと言葉に使用
Real chances don't force us to step on an image. Using this talent and words with this buddy.
さあやっておしまい simon says でも耳を貸すな anyone says
Now let's wrap it up, Simon says, but don't lend an ear to what anyone says.
また来世よりカマスmyselvesだぜ 橋を架けることこそがdream それを渡って向こう岸に行くことがreal
Smashing myselves even more than the next life. Building a bridge is the dream, crossing it to the other shore is real.
いつも半歩先にある好奇心のghostだけが握る俺のリード this is the my will!
Always half a step ahead, only the ghost of curiosity holds my leash, this is the my will!
死んでもいいと思える瞬間を死んでもなお求めている 欲深くも受け取ったマイクですべてを言葉にしたい
Seeking even in death the moment I could die for. Greedily wanting to put everything into words with this mic I received.
神様 俺は世界だけじゃ物足りない 「ごめんね」も「さよなら」も擦り傷にしながら荊道をゆく
God, the world alone isn't enough for me. Walking the thorny path with "sorry" and "goodbye" as scrapes.
僕らだって今手にしたんだ だから歌うよこの場所で
We finally got it in our hands too, so we'll sing right here.
コインと涙を抱きしめて 今叫ぶよ「幸せだ」
Embracing coins and tears, now shouting "I'm happy!"
声が聞こえたんだ "world is yours"
I heard a voice say, "The world is yours."
神様は手のひら返しが上手
God is a master at turning His hand.
geek to da jobs, nemo to da jaws
でも俺のマインドは「触んじゃねえよ、jocks」
But my mindset is "Don't touch me, jocks!"
'cause i'm nerd mother f**ker
'Cause I'm a nerd motherfucker,
rapで現実にする jokes
turning jokes into reality with rap.
すっ転んで こぼれて いった コイン と 涙 の 数 限り ない けれど
Stumbling and spilling over with countless coins and tears...
ただ 走っ た 先 たどり着い た 今 叫ぶ よ 「 幸せ だ 」
I just kept running and arrived, now shouting, "I'm happy!"
Thank you so much, Boogey Voxx!
ありがとう、Calli。
Thank you, Calli.
Thank you!
ありがとう！Thank you, Mutsumi!
Thank you, Mutsumi!
またな！
See ya!
See you around!
Bye-bye!
Thank you so much!
Wow, it's Mori...
えもいね、なんか……
It's so emotional, you know...
すごい。
Wow.
Very emotional.
Man, those guys, they've really been there for me ever since back in the day when I was nobody,
Man, those guys have really been there for me ever since back in the day when I was nobody,
they always cheered me on.
So a big ups to Boogey Voxx for being who they are,
and may their journeys continue and I hope that they still create wonderful things.
and may their journeys continue, and I hope they still create wonderful things.
Thank you so much you guys, that was amazing, I'm glad that you liked it.
Thank you.
Well, I guess now that we're here, um, and it's just me alone again on this big stage,
but I'm not alone because I have wonderful deadbeats, deadbeats everywhere.
but I'm not alone because I have wonderful Deadbeats—Deadbeats everywhere!
I'm not alone because you guys are here, that's always how it's been, thank you so kindly, really truly.
Now, speaking of live shows, I recently made a big announcement about the Calliope Mori New Underworld Order Blu-ray!
Blu-ray, Blu-ray, Blu-ray, Blu-ray!
If you didn't get a chance to get it, check it out, this is how you can find it.
You go to my channel—hey look, that's me—um, you can also check it out in the description of this video.
You go to my channel—hey look, that's me! Um, you can also check it out in the description of this video.
You can find a link to the Blu-ray, but there's the trailer, click that.
Go down, yeah, baby! Thank you for making this video, J-Chad—go down to the description, click that little blue link right there,
Go down—yeah, baby! Thank you for making this video, J-Chad! Go down to the description, click that little blue link right there,
and you can choose what store you get it from, either of those links, okay?
And the shipping may be cheaper if you choose a local place, but if you're in the States, you definitely want to use the Mori Calliope Official Shop,
because the shipping is going to be way, way cheaper there.
Take a look, there's the Blu-ray! And with the limited edition, you get a special tapestry—talk a bit about the tapestry, mo arimasu yo.
Take a look, there's the Blu-ray! And with the limited edition, you get a special tapestry—plus, there's a tapestry, mo arimasu yo.
Check it out, volume ippai! There's so many songs! So many songs!
So, um, it's really a fantastic piece, I would I would really—I would love it if you would check it out,
So, um, it's really a fantastic piece. I would really—I would love it if you would check it out,
especially if you didn't get to see the show.
Um, and then on the Twitter, you can check it out on on the Twitter, on my Twitter, if you scroll down, you can find the tweet there,
Um, and then on Twitter, you can check it out on Twitter—on my Twitter. If you scroll down, you can find the tweet there,
click that link.
Um, as a matter of fact, go ahead and check out and follow the official Mori Calliope artist Twitter.
Uh, that pretty much gets notified about everything right away if you want the earliest news about me and what I'm doing,
That pretty much gets notified about everything right away if you want the earliest news about me and what I'm doing,
go follow the official artist Twitter.
And that's all that I have to say about the Blu-ray, please get the Blu-ray and enjoy, enjoy, show it to your friends and family—just kidding, don't do that.
Um, please enjoy the Blu-ray and enjoy watching all your favorite Mori performances,
because it's it's really amazing and I think the audio has been kind of like specially, you know,
because it's really amazing. And I think the audio has been specially, you know,
put arranged and put together I watched the whole thing. I watched the whole thing and it it's good, it's good.
arranged and put together. I watched the whole thing. I watched the whole thing and it—it's good, it's good.
Um, it's good sound quality is what I'm trying to say, so the sound quality is good.
The sound quality is good, is what I'm trying to say, so the sound quality is good.
Uh now, we also have another thing, as you may all have guessed, I too have 3D merchandise!
Now, we also have another thing. As you may all have guessed, I too have 3D merchandise!
It is, tada!
A very special pendant accessory set.
Now, before you say, "Wait a minute, that's just for the ladies, Calliope Mori, what the heck? I can't get that!" Wrong, wrong you are, anyone can wear this ice,
okay? Anyone, it'll look cool on anybody.
And you know what? If you really don't want to wear it as a necklace, you got two other options, okay?
Two other options, you can kind of, you know, make a keychain yourself, you just take the—you're going to have to, you know, use some tweezers and stuff. You can make a keychain out of it, which is pretty cool.
Or you can set it up just like this as a collector's piece with the special Scythe acrylic, and it just—it hangs down right from there, it's got my signature on it,
Or you can set it up just like this as a collector's piece with the special Scythe acrylic, and it just hangs down right from there. It's got my signature on it,
so you can, you know, put it somewhere special, show your friends, "Hey look, that's the special Mori Calliope pendant."
I really wanted some some cool jewelry for me.
So, um, so anyway, that's uh that is my 3D merchandise is a cute pendant.
So, um, anyway, that is—that is my 3D merchandise, a cute pendant!
so far, right?
Um, with with Ina and Wawa, they had kind of like life essential things.
Um, with Ina and Wawa, they had kind of like life-essential things.
I wanted to do something uh that is kind of like out of the way of that, I guess.
I wanted to do something that is kind of out of the way of that, I guess.
So here's this pendant! Yabta!
So yeah, anyway, you can purchase this after the big myth collab on the fifth.
Uh everybody's 3D merch will be available, so please wait until then.
Everybody's 3D merch will be available, so please wait until then.
Um, I guess that's it.
Wow. We did it. We did a show.
Here, in this big stage, with all of you together with me.
Here, on this big stage, with all of you together with me.
Um, thank you.
Well, before this place burns to the ground, I just want to say thank you so much, everyone.
For always supporting me and for for looking out for me, I'll keep doing my best.
For always supporting me and for looking out for me, I'll keep doing my best.
And I guess I'll catch you on the flip side.
Guess I got to go back to the underworld cuz there's still stuff to do. There's lots more to do.
Guess I got to go back to the underworld 'cause there's still stuff to do. There's lots more to do.
All right. Well, I got to go.
Uh, goodbye, everyone.
Peace!